{
    "question": "Apa bahasa Inggris dia mengernyitkan alisnya?",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "he furrowed his brow",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "bantuin-aku-dong-cari-biografi-aknes-monica-menggunakan-bahasa-in-292",
            "question": "Bantuin aku dong cari Biografi aknes monica menggunakan Bahasa inggris",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Agnes Monica Muljoto. Born in Jakarta 1 July 1986, known abroad as Agnes Mo. She stared her career in the entertainment industry at the age of six as a child singer. She jobs is singer, actress, dancer, voice actress, and producer.",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-keegunaan-dari-whowhosewhomwhichwhere-dalam-adjective-cla-586",
            "question": "apa keegunaan dari who,whose,whom,which,where dalam adjective clause, saya agak kurang mengerti sepenuhnya ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Who\u00a0=\u00a0( Sentences + Adjective Clause + Auxilary/Verb\u00a0) Untuk Subject<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Ex:\u00a0<strong>I saw the man <u>who is </u>tall<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Is =</strong> Auxilary<br><br>Whom =\u00a0( Sentences + Adjective Clause + Subject ) Untuk Subject<u><br></u> \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 Ex:\u00a0<strong>The woman <u>whom you</u> saw last night is my sister<br></strong>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0<strong>You =\u00a0</strong>Subject<br><br>Whose = ( Sentences + Adjective Clause + Noun ) Untuk Subject<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Ex:\u00a0<strong>Santi <u>whose hair</u> is black and lock is beautiful<br></strong><strong>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Hair =\u00a0</strong>Noun<br><br>Which = ( Sentences + Adjective Clause + Aux/S/Verb ) Untuk Object<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Ex:\u00a0<strong>The food <u>which is</u> made of bread and sausage is hot dog<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0The cat <u>which sultan</u> feeds every morning is very funny<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Is =\u00a0</strong>Auxilary<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0\u00a0<strong> Sultan =\u00a0</strong>Subject<br><br>Where = Untuk menjelaskan tempat<br>\u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0 \u00a0Ex:\u00a0<strong>Mall, where we shopping is aweso</strong><strong>me<br></strong><strong><br></strong>Semoga bermanfaat :)\u00a0<br><strong></strong>Jika ingin bertanya, silahkan komen dibawah :)<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-1-contoh-recount-text-732",
            "question": "Buatlah 1 contoh recount text",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "last holiday i went to my grandparents house. me and my family went to a mall",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "coba-sebeutkan-contoh-dari-spoof-dan-kesimpulannya-845",
            "question": "Coba sebeutkan contoh dari spoof dan kesimpulannya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Contoh :<br>Joe&#039;s Mother got angry because her son got a low mark on English test.<br>\n\"Why did you get such a low mark on that test?\" Asked mother angrily. \nAsked by his angry mother, Joe just kept silent and went out.<br>\nA few moment, Joe came back home and met his mother again. His mother asked the same question.<br>\nJoe answered steadily, \"Because of absence.\"<br>\n\"You mean you were absent on the day of the test?\" Mother wondered.<br>\nJoe replied, \"No, but the kid who sits next to me was.\"\n\n<br><br>Kesimpulan :<br><span><span>sebuah teks yang berisi tentang humor meski sebagian teksnya \nsudah dimodifikasi dari aslinya.</span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-dialog-dengan-menggunakan-ungkapan-expression-love-and-sa-467",
            "question": "Buatlah dialog dengan menggunakan ungkapan expression love and sadness beserta situasinya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\n<span>Me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Mom, i should tell you right now</span></span>\n<br><span>\nMom : What is it\ndear ? tell me right now</span>\n<br><span>\n<span>Me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : I should go to australia mom, i get that\nschollarship from school</span></span>\n<br><span>\nMom : Are you\nkidding me ?</span><br>\u00a0<span><span>Me\u00a0 : No mom, i\u2019m seriously this is a special\nchance for me to catch my dream would you like to </span></span>\n<span>\n<span>\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 let me go ?</span></span><br>\u00a0<span><span>mom : But i\nlove you dear how can i let you go ?</span></span>\n<span>\n<span><br>me\u00a0\u00a0 : Calmdown mom everythings gonna be alright</span></span>\n<span>\n<span><br>mom : But ,\ni\u2019m afraid if i\u2019ll miss you my daughter i feel so sad\u00a0 if i let you go</span></span><br>\u00a0<span><span>me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : It\u2019s ok mom, you can call me or message\nme distance is not a big problem</span></span><br>\u00a0<span>mom : If that\u2019s\nyou want i\u2019ll let you go, but you must take care there</span><br>\u00a0<span><span>me\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 : Sure mom\u00a0\nwish me luck</span></span> <span><br>mom : Sure dear</span><span><br><br></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "A : hy...<br>B : hy..<br>A : let&#039;s go to the cinema<br>B : what to do?<br>A : watching movies, now there recent a movie. you know?<br>B : really?? what the movie?<br>A : Harry Poter<br>B : really?? i love that movie. but.....<br>A : why??<br>B : i certainly shouldn&#039;t watch that movie<br>A : why?<br>B : now, i have a lot of tasks. so i will not go.<br>A : no problem. you can watch the next time<br>B : iam so sadness<br>A : be poison<br>B : thank you<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-translate-ke-dalam-bahasa-indonesia-kata-kata-dibawah-ini-822",
            "question": "tolong translate ke dalam bahasa indonesia, kata-kata dibawah ini... Salam perkenalan, selamat bergabung dengan perusahaan kami. Mari kita berjuang sama-sama untuk kemajuan perusahaan dan kesejahteraan para karyawan dan karyawati diperusahaan kita. Dan mari kita sama-sama mempersiapkan tanggungjawab atas kemajuan perusahaan ini.",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Salam perkenalan, selamat bergabung dengan perusahaan kami. Mari kita berjuang sama-sama untuk kemajuan perusahaan dan kesejahteraan para karyawan dan karyawati diperusahaan kita. Dan mari kita sama-sama mempersiapkan tanggungjawab atas kemajuan perusahaan ini.<br><br></span>Introductory greetings, congratulations join our company. Let&#039;s fight together for the progress and welfare of the employees of the company and an employee of the company we are. And let us equally the responsibility for preparing the company&#039;s progress.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>Introductory greetings, congratulations join our company. Let&#039;s struggle are equally for the progress and welfare of the employees of the company and an employee of the company we are. And let us equally the responsibility for preparing this company&#039;s progress<span>.</span></span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "jelasin-tentang-present-perfect-tense-920",
            "question": "Jelasin tentang present perfect tense\u00a0",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Present perfect adalah tenses yang menyatakan bahwa kejadian sudah dilakukan.<br>Rumus : S + Have/Has(Auxiliary) + V3<br>Misal : I have done my homework<br>Unsur : I = Subject<br>Have = Aux/Have/Has<br>Done = V3<br>Homework = Object<br>Umumnya ditambahkan kata Since + Time<br>Jadi : I have done my homework since this morning<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "present perfect itu berhubungan dengan kejadian yang sudah selesai. kata kuncinya sih ada kata \"sudah\", \"baru saja\", dsb.<br><br>misalkan \"saya sudah mengerjakan PR\", atau i have done my homework<br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "berikan-5-kalimat-giving-instruction-312",
            "question": "Berikan 5 kalimat giving instruction",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "aku tulis dalam procedural text, how to make omelete<br>first,crack the eggs<br>after that beat the eggs<br>an then mix it with a salt or meat<br>after that cook it in a hot plate<br>finaly eat the eggs",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "mohon-berikan-contoh-soal-mengenai-persuading-459",
            "question": "Mohon berikan contoh soal mengenai persuading",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Persuading adalah mempengaruhi lawan bicara untuk melakukan atau mengerjakan sesuatu seperti yang diharapkan pihak pertama<br><br>COntoh\u00a0<br>Mengajak bermain basket<br>Hi my brother, would you be so kind to accompany me playing basketball? I will give you a chocolate if you would like to play it with me.\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "when do you go to school about 10 minutes later?",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "contoh-certia-bahasa-inggris-last-vocation-892",
            "question": "Contoh certia bahasa inggris \"last vocation\"",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "It&#039;s curious as we grow older, how easy it is to lose our sense of \ndirection, a sense of vocation, a sense of God&#039;s calling us to important\n things still to be done. Vocations are not just for the young starting \nout in marriage, a career, or religious life. There&#039;s another kind of \nvocation \u2014 a kind of \"late vocation\" \u2014 God&#039;s final call to a strong \nfinish. It is God&#039;s call to each one of us to grow old gracefully \u2014 full\n of grace \u2014 to grow toward Him.    \nGod calls us to respond heroically, like Saint Paul, pouring ourselves \nout like a libation until we can say: \"I have fought the good fight, I \nhave finished the race, I have kept the faith\" (II Tm 7).<span><br><br><br>INI</span>\u00a0?\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}